{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Gottlieb",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1938-03-18",
    "human_readable": "Carl Gottlieb was born on March 18, 1938.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9413714408874512,
            "question": "Is Carl Gottlieb's birthdate before or after March 15th, 1938?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.910301148891449,
            "question": "When was Carl Gottlieb born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887462317943573,
            "question": "What century was Carl Gottlieb born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8160102367401123,
            "question": "On which day was Carl Gottlieb born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7716417908668518,
            "question": "What month was Carl Gottlieb born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731522798538208,
            "question": "What is Carl Gottlieb's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6531717777252197,
            "question": "Does Carl Gottlieb's birthdate fall in the first half or second half of March?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5523087382316589,
            "question": "In what year did Carl Gottlieb come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5438430905342102,
            "question": "How old would Carl Gottlieb be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4532133638858795,
            "question": "If today is March 19th, is Carl Gottlieb's birthday today or yesterday?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Gottlieb was born on March 18, 1938.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5563_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Carl Gottlieb be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5563_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Carl Gottlieb come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5563_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Carl Gottlieb's birthdate fall in the first half or second half of March?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5563_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5563_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Carl Gottlieb was born on March 18, 1938."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}